<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Usage on Ashita v4 Documentation</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Usage on Ashita v4 Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configurations</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/configurations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/configurations/</guid><description>This page is subject to change heavily in the future when Ashita v4 gains its full UI launcher.
Once you have downloaded and extracted/installed Ashita, you are ready to begin configurations.
Configuration File Locations Ashita includes its own built-in ConfigurationManager object which makes use of .ini files. To help keep things organized, all configuration files that make use of this system are stored in a central location, the /config/ folder.</description></item><item><title>[Beta] Running Ashita</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/running/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/running/</guid><description>We currently do not have a graphical user interface made for launching Ashita v4 during the beta. This documentation covers using the ashita-cli.exe launcher until a full UI launcher is ready.
Before you attempt to launch/run Ashita v4, please be sure to create a new boot configuration file with your desired configurations. You can find more information in regards to configurations here: Configurations
Once you have setup a new boot configuration file, you are ready to launch Ashita.</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/commands/</guid><description>Command Syntax Commands implemented within Ashita all follow the below format for their arguments. This helps keep usage unified across all commands. It also makes documentation easier to follow when all commands make use of the same format.
Syntax Description text Required; entered as shown. &amp;lt;text&amp;gt; Required argument. &amp;lt;text...&amp;gt; Required argument. (Multiple arguments accepted.) (text|text) Required, one of. [text] Optional argument. [text...] Optional argument. (Multiple arguments accepted.) Note: Arguments surrounded with &amp;lt; and &amp;gt; are considered positional, meaning their order matters.</description></item><item><title>Text Scripts</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/scripts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/usage/scripts/</guid><description>One of Ashita&amp;rsquo;s built-in features is the ability to execute text-based scripts which can contain additional commands to be executed within them. Scripts were originally created to vastly improve on the games extremely limited macro system (PS2 limitations!) by allowing players to execute more than six command entries, having multiple waits, and doing more than just normal game related functions.
As the client has gained new features (ie. gear sets, more macro space via books, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>