<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Download &amp; Install on Ashita v4 Documentation</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/</link><description>Recent content in Download &amp; Install on Ashita v4 Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>System Requirements</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/requirements/</guid><description>In order to make use of Ashita, there are some requirements you will need to install. While some of these are optional, it is suggested to install everything listed on this page to ensure anything you may use with Ashita, or additional third-party tooling, works without dependency issues.
Supported Operating Systems Ashita supports the following operating systems:
Windows 7 (Must install latest service packs.) Windows 8, Windows 8.1 Windows 10 Windows 11 While Ashita may work on other operating systems not listed above, we do not give any kind of direct support for them!</description></item><item><title>[Beta] Install via Git</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/install_git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/install_git/</guid><description>Installing and updating the Ashita v4 beta using Git is considered more advanced. If you are not familiar with or comfortable with using Git, you can instead install (or update) using the latest repository snapshot.
See Install via Zip for more information.
Currently, the recommended method of installing the Ashita v4 beta is by using a Git client. At this time, the latest beta release is maintained in a single GitHub repository which makes it easy to find the main project files and first-party addons/plugins in one place.</description></item><item><title>[Beta] Install via Zip</title><link>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/install_zip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://docs.ashitaxi.com/installation/install_zip/</guid><description>It is recommended that you use Git to install the Ashita v4 beta for easy updating. See Install via Git if you are comfortable doing so.
Picking An Installation Folder When picking a folder to install Ashita to, it is important that you DO NOT break the following guidelines:
Ashita should NOT be installed into a system protected folder.
This means it should not be put into folders (or folders within) such as:</description></item></channel></rss>